http://www.bmwlinks.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
At BMWLinks, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit BMWLinks.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.
Log Files
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
Email newsletters related cookies
This site offers newsletter or email subscription services and cookies may be used to remember if you are already registered and whether to show certain notifications which might only be valid to subscribed/unsubscribed users.
Site preferences cookies
In order to provide you with a great experience on this site we provide the functionality to set your preferences for how this site runs when you use it. In order to remember your preferences we need to set cookies so that this information can be called whenever you interact with a page is affected by your preferences.
Cookies and Web Beacons
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.
We also use third party advertisements on BMWLinks to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.
This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing London real estate ads to someone in London, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit this address: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html.
DoubleClick DART cookies
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”).
The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx
Disabling Cookies
You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.
Other third party cookies
Some parts of the content shown on the website can be sourced from external sources, which can add their own cookies, called “third-party cookies”. Specifically:
YouTube: embedded videos – privacy policy https://support.google.com/youtube/answer/7671399?hl=ro
Vimeo: embeded videos – privacy policy https://vimeo.com/privacy
Twitter: embedded tweets – privacy policy https://twitter.com/en/privacy
Instagram: embedded instagram posts – privacy policy https://help.instagram.com/519522125107875?helpref=page_content
Google Analytics: anonymous web traffic statistic
details https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245
settings / opt-out https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
Google Adsense/Doubleclick: online advertisements – settings https://www.google.com/settings/ads
Google reCAPTCHA: anti-spam/anti-bot – details https://www.google.com/intl/policies/privacy/
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads
Bing: https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads
Amazon: https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/
Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.
Changes
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
Contact us
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us at hello@bmwlinks.com
Contact
Write for Us
Privacy Policy
Floor Mats for BMW
Copyright © 2020. BMW Links. All rights reserved
Home
BMW Forums
BMW Dealerships
